We're here in response to the accident
that happened
in the set of Joyce Trinidad's film.
Wait, Deedee couldn't possibly do
what you're thinking.
She's innocent!
That's how I can protect myself
from Joyce's revelation.
Is that how easy it is for you, Dad?
Isn't that what you want, too?
To eliminate that woman?
We'll get through this.
What happened to my daughter?
You can only talk to me decently
if my daughter is okay.
If something happens to my daughter,
I will blame no one else but you!
4:46 AM, time of death.
No, no, no, no.
I am my daughter's number one fan.
She would look for me in the audience
when she competes in beauty pageants.
And she'd cry.
She'd cry when she couldn't find me.
She said... She said I was...
I was her lucky charm.
That's why she would always win.
But I wonder...
if I actually bring bad luck into her life?
Uncle...
Why did I have to come see her at work
on the set?
Why did I tell her what I knew?
I got her involved.
I dragged her into this mess!
Uncle...
My dear Joyce died
carrying that burden in her heart.
Uncle Edmond, what do you mean?
What did you tell Joyce?
Love...
I know it must be devastating
for you and the whole team.
I'm already scheduled...
to talk with the police.
Everyone else has already been interrogated.
I feel bad for Deedee.
She's now the main suspect.
Love, you never know, right? Maybe...
Maybe the police are just overly suspicious
of everyone.
But maybe...
it's just a simple case of neglect, right?
Maybe they overlooked the gun.
Maybe they didn't change the bullets, right?
- That's all there is to it.
- Via...
Via, it's so painful.
So much.
It hurts so much.
Via...
there's no one else to blame but me.
Via, because...
We were already separated.
We've been apart.
But I...
I insisted on working with her.
If only... I didn't come back to her life.
I wish...
I wish her life would have been different.
I wish I had avoided her.
What are you saying?
This is all my fault.
It's all my fault.
No.
Liam, no.
It's not you.
It's not your fault. It's not you.
Dad saw this video. And he knows him.
Where's Uncle Edmond? Can I talk to him?
It will help my investigation.
- Let's go and see him.
- You can't talk to him, Hans.
You can't do that
with his condition right now.
Uncle, calm down.
Whatever it was that you told her,
it was not your fault, Uncle.
Joyce would not want
to see you like that, Uncle.
I'm sure she wants you
to be in good condition.
Calm down, okay?
That kid always thinks about me.
Honestly, you should talk to Liam Herrera.
I wonder why you're talking to Blacksmith.
They all left me.
That's the reason why
you're a person of interest.
Because you have a motive to be angry
at your employees
who joined Liam and Joyce's production.
Okay, fine.
Start the interrogation
so we can get this over and done with.
This is just an initial investigation.
We couldn't talk to them on the set
because it was chaotic,
and everyone was already emotional.
Sir Vergil, sorry for getting you involved.
Okay, Police Officer Cruz.
We're willing to cooperate.
I feel sorry for Deedee.
She's like a sister to me.
She's been receiving death threats already...
from angry fans.
Her family is getting dragged into it, too.
We were okay on the set.
It was not an inside job or foul play.
No one would deliberately kill Joyce.
Right, Director Phil?
What now, Director Phil?
Why are you suddenly speechless?
Do you think
I don't know what you say about me?
That I still hold a grudge against Joyce?
I know you think I was behind what happened.
Maxine, I didn't say anything like that.
We're in front of police officers.
You know that's oral defamation.
Stop arguing.
We keep Hernandez under our custody
because her family requested it.
You said so yourself.
This case is high profile.
And she has received
a lot of death threats already.
Unless someone else is willing
to get detained too.
Okay.
We'll just keep you updated
with developments in our investigation.
[Photos]
Son.
Are you ashamed to show me
that you're crying for Joyce?
No, Mom.
I feel guilty.
I feel guilty because...
maybe I'm making Via feel...
that I'm sorry for losing Joyce.
She might think that I'm being insensitive.
But, Mom...
I can't help it.
I can't help but get hurt.
Son.
There's nothing wrong about mourning.
You know what?
You're my son.
I'll be the last one to judge you.
Is there something you wish to tell me?
The day...
that Joyce died...
I told her I love her, Mom.
Joyce... I want to tell you something.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing, son?
Because I know that you're hurting for Via.
You know what, son?
I reminded you
that Via was your girlfriend...
because I knew
you have been feeling something else.
Son, I was...
I was pushing Via to you because...
Because I don't want her to end up like me.
Someone who got neglected.
But I forgot to check...
what you really felt.
I'm sorry, son...
if I stopped you from being happy
and choosing what you really want.
Now it's too late.
Even though...
I wasn't able to tell her sooner...
I hope
that after everything we'd been through...
After everything we learned
from each other...
while fulfilling each other's
dreams together...
I hope I got to make her feel my love...
That I love her so much.
Oh, son...
[In Memoriam, Joyce, 1995-2022]
Boss, can I ask you something?
Where's the man
who lives on the other corner?
Who?
The homeless man?
He's no longer there.
The authorities forced him to relocate.
It's really illegal to stay there.
Is that so?
Okay, thank you so much.
Okay.
Let me have some of it.
Get out of here! You stink!
Hey, that's mine!
Your girlfriend doesn't love you!
[40 days later]
Please, pray for us.
Hail, Virgin Mary, conceived without sin.
In the name
of the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Coffee.
Thank you.
Days have gone by so fast.
It has been 40 days since Joyce passed away.
I still can't accept it.
I've been crying for 40 days.
I will probably cry until tomorrow.
I don't know how long I will cry.
Joyce!
She's like a sister to me.
Odet.
Why, Madam?
Please show them the way out.
Odet, they might think you're a relative.
Madam, even though Joyce and I
were not related by blood,
I still treated her like family.
This way to the exit.
Let's go.
This way.
Come on.
Madam, please leave the coffee here.
It's bad luck.
You can't take it with you.
This way.
This is the last of Joyce's stuff
in her old room.
Are we going to bury it, too?
This is the first gown she bought
from her savings.
She wore this in several competitions.
You know what?
She couldn't sleep without this.
I can still smell her scent.
What else is here?
What do I do with her cell phone?
I don't know her password.
I can't access it.
I'm sure she has lots of memories here.
Can I borrow it, Auntie?
Okay.
How did you unlock it?
Auntie, when I was courting Joyce,
she asked that we exchange passwords...
until she could return my feelings.
That way, we can be assured
that we're not entertaining other people.
But, Auntie...
we never checked each other's phones.
Because I trust her.
And I know that she trusts me too.
I'm the only one who meddled in her life.
I love your daughter so much.
My daughter is so beautiful.
She's so beautiful.
You two look so good together.
You look so good together.
I'm recording this...
in case something happens to me,
because of the information I have.
Hans, I know you have access to my phone.
I know you can unlock this.
I have crucial information about the case
you're investigating in Casa Fuerte.
About the construction worker who died.
This is about Lando, the suspect,
and his boss, Congressman Ramon dela Peña.
If you keep doing your job well
until I become the President...
I'll take care of you, my friend.
Don't try to fight.
Put your hands up.
Go on. Put handcuffs on them.
Attorney Hans, everything is fine now.
Don't move!
Put your hands up!
You're caught red-handed.
What's the meaning of this?
We'll explain at the police station.
What will happen to us now?
I think I'm going to lie low for now.
I'm still waiting for Boss Bro's call.
I have nothing to do
with all your accusations.
Watch this.
We'll talk at the police station!
[Blacksmith Productions involved
in Joyce's murder?]
Hey, be careful!
It's been 40 days
since Joyce Trinidad passed away.
And there's a big revelation
that can give justice to her death.
After 40 days,
a video recording was found by her mother,
where Joyce revealed her alleged killer.
It is said
that behind Joyce's murder
is a bigger crime connected
to the illegal business of a syndicate
allegedly headed
by Congressman Ramon dela Peña.
What's going on?
This involved the companies
that the congressman had invested in.
That includes
the Herrera Group of Companies,
Casa Fuerte Properties,
Blacksmith Productions, and many others.
Son...
Your dad...
Is Danilo...
Is Danilo involved in it?
Is he working with the people
who killed Joyce?
My God.
But, son...
You don't know about that, right?
You have no knowledge
of Casa Fuerte's illegal dealings
because you're no longer there, right?
You have nothing to do with it, right, son?
Deedee!
- Dee!
- Dee.
The truth is out.
We already know who killed Miss Joyce.
Until the last moment,
Miss Joyce has helped you clear your name.
I'm happy
that Miss Joyce got the justice she deserved.
Liam.
Son...
Tell me.
You don't know about it, do you?
Son...
There's no one to blame but me.
We were already separated from each other.
I insisted on working with her again.
If only I didn't return to her life,
things would have been different.
This is my fault.
It's not you.
Not you, not you.
I'm sorry, Love.
I'm sorry, Liam.
- I'm sorry.
- Isn't that what you also want?
Deep inside your heart...
To get rid of that woman.
To get rid of that woman,
isn't that what you want, too?
No, no, no.
No, no, no!
No.
- Dad.
- Son.
I'm sorry.
I hope you can forgive me.
I couldn't break free from Ramon.
I couldn't do what you did.
Dad...
It's my fault...
that you're here.
Everything started with me.
What pains me more...
is knowing I'm the reason Joyce died.
Congressman Ramon targeted her...
because of what she knew.
That monster did
what he had threatened to do.
If only I knew...
If only I knew, I could have done something
before he could make a move.
I am more culpable than you are.
Ramon is in your life because of me.
Dad, no.
I'm willing to pay for all my sins.
I'll take responsibility for it.
Save yourself.
What will happen to your mom
if you go to jail?
You have nothing to do with these cases.
I'll own up to everything.
Liam...
I have lots of shortcomings as your father.
I couldn't take responsibility
for you and your mother,
even though Tess is the one I really love.
I forced myself to be with my wife and Vergil
even though we weren't happy.
I couldn't follow my heart.
So now, let me be a father to you
the way I know how.
I'm begging you.
Do as I tell you.
Just let me be.
I'll take full responsibility.
Save yourself.
Miss Via!
Queenie here.
Miss Via?
I'm going in, okay?
Miss Via.
Miss Via!
What's that?
Holy crap. I don't read such things.
Don't you have any sexy magazines?
Here you go, boss.
There.
That's what I'm talking about.
Via...
How are you?
Do you need anything?
Are you hungry?
Stay in bed for now.
I'll take care of everything.
Why did you do that?
Good thing Queenie helped you
cough out those pills.
I need to tell you something.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Sorry for what?
I'm sorry, Liam.
It's all my fault.
It was me who told Dad.
I told him about Joyce's discovery.
I heard her.
She was talking to her father.
Her father knows a lot.
He used to work for my dad.
So he knows about all of
my dad's illegal dealings.
Love...
Sorry.
It's my fault.
I got scared.
I got scared that my dad would go to jail.
So... so I told him about Joyce.
I just got scared.
I only wanted to protect my dad.
I'm the reason...
I'm the reason Joyce died.
Liam.
Liam...
Liam, please forgive me.
Sorry... Sorry.
I know... I know you love Joyce, okay?
I know you love her,
but I didn't intend for her to die.
I didn't know that this would happen to her.
I didn't know, Liam.
I didn't know that this would happen.
I only protected my dad, Liam.
I thought he would go to jail.
I didn't know.
I didn't want this to happen, Love.
Forgive me, please. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
Please... Please.
Please, Love.
I really didn't know. Believe me.
Please, believe me.
I didn't know.
I didn't know that would happen.
Please.
Love...
[Your warmth and shine
left the world a better place]
[Joycelyn A Trinidad]
[Savana]
It hurts when you love someone, right?
Have you made up your mind, Boss Bro?
Sorry, Borj.
I am not the Boss Bro you think I am.
I did bad things...
that led to Joyce's death.
I have no choice...
but to take responsibility for everything.
I tolerated...
I tolerated the Congressman's illegal dealings
in Casa Fuerte.
So I'm not innocent, Borj.
Are you turning yourself in?
Does Ma'am Tess know?
Maybe I'll tell her when I get home.
Do you want me to go with you?
Borj...
The help you can do for me right now...
is to keep away from me.
I won't let you get involved...
when I turn myself in.
Boss Bro...
I promise...
I will visit you often.
Borj...
Thank you.
I guess it's time I man up.
I want to be your wife.
I'm so happy.
So happy that it's overwhelming.
I'm glad you accepted my offer
to work together again, Liam.
I'm willing to work with you.
What's your motive, Liam?
What do you want to happen?
Why are you interested in this case?
So that we can give justice
to Siloy's death and Uncle Edmond's blindness.
What's...
You're the man I always dream about.